WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - Minister of Finland (Part 1); "The Shadow" from Mutual Program (Number 3), 10/08/1939; wsyr_radio_105; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Obliterated label side - The Shadow - "Baseball game", Part 2 of 2, Blue Coal, sponsor, Mutual Network, Oct. 8, 1939. Other side - His Excellency Yalma (?) J. - Minister of Republic of Finland at Outbreak of WW2, Neutrality History. Mutual Network Broadcast from WOL in Washington, D. C.
  - "Mr. District Attorney" (part 2); President Roosevelt - "Navy day speech" (part 2), 10/22/1941; 10/27/1941; wsyr_radio_162; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Mr. President Franklin Roosevelt to Dwight Eisenhower (closed circuit), parts 1 and 3, wsyr_radio_076; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 12)
  - Mr. President Franklin Roosevelt to Dwight Eisenhower (closed circuit), parts 2 and 4, wsyr_radio_077; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 12)
  - Mrs. Wainwright on husband’s release; Romilo [?], wsyr_radio_279; wife of General Jonathan Mayhew Wainwright, 1883-1953, who was held as a prisoner of war, eventual winner of the Congressional Medal of Honor; labels damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Murray Bernthal - Olmstead Victrola Shop, 01/18/1948; wsyr_radio_437; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Murray Bernthal - Olmstead Victrola Shop for Sunday; Spots, 07/23/1948; 08/01/1948; wsyr_radio_438; note on sleeve reads: "Ruth - I did a line show last nite - would like to save this one for next Sunday when I’ll be away. M."; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Murray Bernthal - Olmstead Victrola Shop; North Farm and Home (part 2), 02/17/1946; wsyr_radio_428; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Mutual Radio Networks - Mutual Broadcasting System - Mutual Black Network: Demo Tape No. 1, wsyr_radio_925; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
    1 - Comprehensive News I - 5 minutes on a Good Music Station; 2 - Comprehensive News I - 1 minute on a Wall-to-Wall Music Station; 3 - Comprehensive News II - 5 minutes on All News Station; 4 - Comprehensive News II - 2 minute on a Country Station; 5 - Progressive News - 4 minutes on a Country Station; 6 - Progressive News - 1 1/2 minutes on a Progressive Rock Station; 7 - Jack Anderson; 8 - Jimmy the Greek; 9 - Operation News Line; 10 Reporter’s Round-Up; 11 - Mutual Commentators: Duff Thomas; Fulton Lewis III; Forrest Boyd; Robert F. Hurleigh
  - Mutual Radio Networks - Mutual Broadcasting System - Mutual Black Network: Demo Tape No. 2, wsyr_radio_926; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
    1 - Wide Weekend of Sports; 2 - NFL Monday Night Football; 3 - Notre Dame Football; 4 - NCAA Basketball; 5 - Major League Baseball; 6 - Championship Boxing; 7 - Mutual Sports; 8 - Nightwatch; 9 - Country Music Spectacular; 10 - Mutual News Year-End Review
  - N. Y. Times Editorial on Flag Day read by Alan Milair, 06/14/1940; wsyr_radio_618; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - NBC Correspondents for NBC & WSYR news, wsyr_radio_598; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
    Correspondents listed on note inside box: # 1 Pauline Frederick; # 2 Merrill Mueller; # 3 Robert Goralski; # 4 John Rich; # 5 Bernard Frizell; # 6 Irving R. Levine; # 7 Howard Tuckner
  - NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: "Quarantine" speech at Chicago; Annual message to Congress; Fireside chat after the outbreak of war (part 2); Lend-lease" Message to Congress (continued); Fireside chat before Pan-American Union Board; Labor Day broadcast; Warning to Axis Vessels (part 4), 10/05/1937; 01/04/1939; 09/03/1939; 01/06/1941; 05/27/1941; 09/11/1941; wsyr_radio_303; VinylDisc
    Side 1: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: "Quarantine" speech at Chicago; Annual message to Congress; Fireside chat after the outbreak of war, Part 2 (#10); Side 2: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: "Lend-lease" Message to Congress (continued); Fireside chat before Pan-American Union Board; Labor Day broadcast; Warning to Axis Vessels, Part 4 (#10)
  - NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: First Inaugural address; Second Inaugural address (part 1), Third Acceptance speech; Fireside chat on National Security; "Lend-lease" Message to Congress, 03/04/1933; 01/20/1937; 08/19/1940; 12/29/1940; 01/06/1941; wsyr_radio_302; VinylDisc
    Side 1: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: First Inaugural address; Second Inaugural address, Part 1 (#10); Side 2: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: Third Acceptance speech; Fireside chat on National Security; "Lend-lease" Message to Congress, Part 3 (#10)
  - NBC Documentary Recordings: Rendezvous with destiny, 12/08/1941; 01/06/1942; 02/23/1942; 07/06/1944; 10/21/1944; wsyr_radio_304; VinylDisc
    Side 1: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: "State of War" message to Congress; "State of Union" message to Congress; Washington’s Birthday address, Part 5 (#10); Side 2: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: Prayer on D-Day; Foreign Policy speech, Part 7 (#10)
  - NBC Documentary Recordings: Rendezvous with destiny, 09/03/1942; 12/24/1943; 01/20/1945; 03/01/19445; 04/16/1945; wsyr_radio_305; VinylDisc
    Side 1: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: Speech to International Student Assembly; Cairo and Teheran report, Part 6 (#10); Side 2: NBC Documentary Recordings - Rendezvous with destiny - Franklin D. Roosevelt: Fourth Inaugural address; Report to Congress on the Crimea Conference; Jefferson Day address, read by Carleton Smith; Tribute by President Truman, Part 8 (#10)
  - NBC European Crisis; Kourt Jacob, 08/26/1939; wsyr_radio_118; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - NBC London broadcast. King George - "Opening Day of War", 09/01/1939; 09/03/1939; wsyr_radio_115; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - NBC News: Reading Writing and Reefer, Edwin Newman, 12/11/1978; wsyr_radio_999; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - NBC Radio tribute to late Brigadier General David Sarnoff, Nov 1971; wsyr_radio_970; tribute to David Sarnoff, founder Radio Corporation of America and National Broadcasting Company (7:05:30 PM to 7:29:30 PM); 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 24:00 (Box 56)
  - NBC Radio: Vice President Spiro Agnew Resigns and NBC News On The Hour (7:30-7:52 PM), 10/15/1973; wsyr_radio_986; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:00 (Box 57)
  - NBC Sounders (DUB), Nov 1973; wsyr_radio_1010; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
    News Opens; Promo; Sounders: News On The Hour; Instant News Special; Hotlines; Update; Chimes; News On the Hour
  - NBC Sounders (Master), Nov 1973; wsyr_radio_1009; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - NBC Special on Ex Vice President, 10/10/1973; wsyr_radio_985; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 57)
  - NBC Special: Pope John Paul II, 10/16/1979; wsyr_radio_550; NBC News Feed, 5:30 PM.; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:10 (Box 19)
  - NBC War Crisis (part 2); Translation of German demands, 08/31/1939; wsyr_radio_114; NBC Blue Network at 4 PM; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Neighborly News from the Ontario Weeklies, Andy Clarke; WSYR radio show: Matinee with Wally and Jane, wsyr_radio_006; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1 (labeled): CBC - Canadian Broadcasting Co., "Neighborly News" from the "Ontario Weeklies", Andy Clarke, WW2 era. Other side - music dubs cuts 1-4. Cut 5 - a segment from a WSYR radio show: "Matinee with Wally and Jane", Fred Jeske, Firman; Russ Russel"
  - New Channels Alarm, Alan Milair spots, wsyr_radio_633; note in box reads: "ACR #341 for Alan, (audio copy of New channels)"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 4:54 (Box 25)
  - Newhouse II Dedication Dinner, 05/30/1974; wsyr_radio_505; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 75:00 (Box 16)
    Broadcast portion of Dinner (9:30-10:45 PM approx.) honoring Mr. + Mrs. S.I. Newhouse, Thursday, May 30, 1974 - Persian Terrace, Hotel Syracuse (Eve of Dedication of Newhouse II), David Brinkley, Master of Ceremonies.
  - News & Views - Black Perspective, 08/01/1971; wsyr_radio_861; host Dennis Dowdell; guests: Mrs. Joyce Tabb, Assistant Director of Urban League On the Job Training Program, Mr. James Hancock, Director Urban League On the Job Training Program; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 13:30 (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 124), 01/13/1974; wsyr_radio_862; guests Dr. Beard and Dr. Francis; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 168), 01/24/1974; wsyr_radio_863; guests Webb Reid, Joyce Tabb, Andrew Willis; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 250), 06/06/1976; wsyr_radio_864; Sickle Cell Anemia, Economic Development, Education, guests: Andrew Willis, Burt Aldamuy; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 251), 06/11/1976; 06/13/1976; wsyr_radio_865; School Integration, guests: Dr. Robert Cecile, Jon Buzzard, Floyd Arnold, Mrs. Marjorie White; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 252), 06/18/1976; 06/20/1976; wsyr_radio_866; Tom Shropshire, Vice President Market Planning Miller Brewing Company; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 253), 06/23/1976; 06/27/1976; 07/04/1976; wsyr_radio_867; High school graduation and future, guests: Pam Noel, Locksley Spencer, Carole Bilson; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:40 (Box 47)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 257), 08/01/1976; wsyr_radio_871; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 258), 08/08/1976; 08/15/1976; wsyr_radio_873; Dunbar Center, guests: George Cossey, Oliver Edwards, Bob Reece, Ronald Jenkins; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 259), 07/30/1976; 08/15/1976; wsyr_radio_874; guests: Reed Wright, Neil Fair; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 261), 08/20/1976; 09/05/1976; wsyr_radio_875; Jr. Achievement and Royalettes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 262), 08/27/1976; 08/29/1976; wsyr_radio_876; Gilbert, Edwards, Chaplains; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 274), 11/19/1976; 11/28/1976; wsyr_radio_877; guests: Lee War, teacher, Jim Miller, teacher, Charlene Burnette, Diane Simcox [?], Amos Nicks, student Roosevelt School; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 276), 12/03/1976; 02/28/1977; wsyr_radio_878; guest: Ed Moyr [?]; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 283), 01/14/1977; 02/06/1977; wsyr_radio_879; School Integration, guests: Mrs. Marjorie White, Mrs. Audrey Haskell, Barry Weinheimer, Diane Gethers; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 285), 01/28/1977; 02/20/1977; wsyr_radio_880; Black colleges; guest: Dr. Frederick Humphries, President of Tennessee State University; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 286), 01/31/1977; 02/13/1977; wsyr_radio_881; guests Frank T Wood, Jr., Pearl Seals; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 287), 02/14/1977; 02/27/1977; wsyr_radio_882; television; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 288), 03/02/1977; 03/06/1977; wsyr_radio_883; Civic Center, guest: Dr. J. Golden; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 289), 03/11/1977; 03/13/1977; wsyr_radio_884; Recitations and singing, guests Rev. Hyrd Seals, Sr. and members The Church of God In Christ, (COGIC); 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 290), 03/18/1977; 03/20/1977; wsyr_radio_885; Hillbrook Detention Home, guests: John Harmon, Dennis Destefano, Geri Boyd; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 327), 11/16/1977; 11/27/1977; 12/04/1977; wsyr_radio_886; Soul Generation (3); 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 384) [missing], 01/10/1979; 01/28/1979; wsyr_radio_887; BOCES, guests: Irvin Henry, District Superintendent, Onondaga-Madison BOCES, Bernice Kipfer, Director H. E. L. P., BOCES., Dr. Frank Ambrosie, Assistant Superintendent Occupational Education, BOCES; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:57 (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 392), 03/18/1979; wsyr_radio_888; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 450), 04/24/1980; wsyr_radio_889; Federal Contract Compliance, with Weldon Rougeau, Q: Perspective; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:00 (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (No. 467), 09/06/1980; 09/07/1980; wsyr_radio_890; Discussing Education Today, guest: Dr. Joseph Wood, Vice Principal Eastwood Middle; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:00 (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (Program No. 254), 06/25/1976; 07/11/1976; wsyr_radio_868; Pre-K, guests: Shirley Davis, Joyce Arthur, Barbara Thorpe, Dorothy Vanderven, Odessa Adams; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (Program No. 255), 07/02/1976; 07/18/1976; wsyr_radio_869; guest Frank Cleckley; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective (Program No. 256), 07/25/1976; wsyr_radio_870; Housing, guests: John Osta, Larry Jackson, Dave Michel, Peter White; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective [episode number unknown], 05/23/1976; 10/15/1982; 10/17/1982; 10/24/1982; wsyr_radio_891; Co-ordinator Nate G. Nichols, Huntington Family Center; Our Community; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective [episode number unknown], 04/16/1978; 10/24/1982; 10/31/1984; wsyr_radio_892; guest: Van Robinson, Co-convener of Syracuse Political Action Neighborhood Conference, (SPANC); 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - News & Views - Black Perspective: Boston Special, 08/03/1976; 08/08/1976; wsyr_radio_872; Urban League, guests: Clarence Barney, Sam H. Jones; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:45 (Box 48)
  - News and Business, wsyr_radio_613; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
    Dick Hoffman - Business Today; Charlie Hocut - "Winters Mens Shop"; 6PM News - World & national, Alan Milair, reporting; Richard Gordon space walk cut short; Gemini program; Grand Jury indicts Stokeley Carmichael in Atlanta; Bill Rapp Commercial, sponsor; Weather; "Country house", commercial); Fred Hillegar local news,(incomplete); SU strike - Building and ground workers; Blue Cross & Blue Shield Commercial; Reelection of Rockefeller?
  - News Block - Premiere (5:30-6:05 PM), 06/05/1972; wsyr_radio_979; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 48:00 (Box 56)
  - News Probe - Transportation, wsyr_radio_589; note reads: "PB 12/21 & 12/26".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 22)
  - News Probe: Gasoline & you, wsyr_radio_586; note reads: "PB: 7/26 & 8/1".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:40 (Box 22)
  - News Probe: Metropolitan Government (Guest - Michael Reagan and Edward Keanse), wsyr_radio_587; note reads: "PB: 8/6 & 8/22; 3M - #175 1 1/5 m.l"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 22)
  - Newsprobe - Drugs: An Update, 12/30/1978; wsyr_radio_553; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:00 (Box 20)
  - Newsprobe: (B-29) Racial Balance in (Syracuse) City Schools, Andrew Willis, Janet Edison, Dennis Sweney, 06/04/1976; 06/06/1976; wsyr_radio_809; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:20 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: A New Agenda for the Elderly, 07/09/1978; wsyr_radio_547; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 19)
  - Newsprobe: A Question of Balance, 12/08/1976; 12/17/1976; 01/09/1977; wsyr_radio_818; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: A visit with Governor Carey, 04/05/1976; wsyr_radio_807; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:30 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Berle interview, 08/07/1978; 08/28/1978; 09/03/1978; wsyr_radio_840; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Business Climate of New York State, 03/31/1976; 04/10/1979; wsyr_radio_804; guest Commissioner John Dyson; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Cost of Electricity, 12/08/1976; 12/10/1976; 12/14/1976; wsyr_radio_816; guests: Ms. Margared [?] Pooler, New York State Board of Consumer Affairs, Mr. Mark De Michele, Vice President Niagara Mohawk, moderators: Rom Hastinos [?], Dom Edwards; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:48 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Crime Knows No Limits, 08/30/1977; wsyr_radio_830; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Day in Life of Eugene Turner (4), 10/28/1977; 11/27/1977; wsyr_radio_824; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Day in Life of firefighter Bruce Conner, 03/24/1976; 04/04/1976; wsyr_radio_825; note on box reads: Complete with open and close; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:05 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Day in the Life of Beulah Durr, 01/28/1977; 01/30/1977; wsyr_radio_820; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:31 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Day in the Life of Earl Johnson, 04/19/1977; 04/24/1977; wsyr_radio_822; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Day in the Life of Mark Smith, 03/25/1977; 04/17/1977; wsyr_radio_821; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Downtown Syracuse, 04/09/1976; 04/25/1976; wsyr_radio_806; guests: R. Balderson [?] and Irving [?] Davis; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Education and the Dollar Crunch (3), 05/27/1977; 06/05/1977; wsyr_radio_826; special program Audio Dub for Radio; note on box reads: "Laura Hand [?]; Has TV 3 Intro." Note on tape reads: "7:30PM"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:05 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Employment, 06/03/1977; 06/26/1977; wsyr_radio_827; guest: Bruce Pierce; special program Audio Dub for Radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:48 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Environmental Conversation, 11/21/1976; wsyr_radio_814; guest: Peter Berle, Commissioner of the Department of New York State Departmental Conservation; special program TV audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Food For Thought, 08/07/1978; wsyr_radio_548; overeating and diet; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 19)
  - Newsprobe: From Here to There, 07/13/1978; 07/17/1978; wsyr_radio_839; guests: Warren Frank, Executive Director Centro, Sally Johnston, President Syracuse Disabled in Action; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: High Cost of Hospitalization, 06/27 [no year]; wsyr_radio_540; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:40 (Box 19)
  - Newsprobe: Holocaust Experience, 04/27/1978; 04/30/1978; wsyr_radio_835; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: In Sickness and In Health, 12/21/1977; 01/08/1977; wsyr_radio_819; health care and preventive medicine; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:05 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Mario Cuomo, N.Y. Secretary of State, 03/20/1977; wsyr_radio_541; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 19)
  - Newsprobe: Precious Memories, conversations with Ernest Johnson, 04/20/1976; 04/25/1976; wsyr_radio_808; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:53 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: School Days - School Daze [sic] with Herb Weisbaum (4), Dec 6 [no year]; Jan 1 [no year]; wsyr_radio_841; drug abuse; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:20 (Box 46)
  - Newsprobe: Solid Waste (3), 05/26/1977; 05/29/1977; wsyr_radio_823; note on the label reads: "Has TV intro"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Solid Waste as Fuel, 04/01/1976; 04/11/1976; wsyr_radio_805; guests John Mulroy, Dr. Charles Johnson; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:20 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Stadium Feasibility, 06/18/1976; 06/20/1976; wsyr_radio_810; guests: Mc Arllife [?], Winters [?], Searles [?]; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Syracuse, 07/09/1976; 07/18/1976; wsyr_radio_811; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Syracuse Schools, 12/01/1976; 12/03/1976; 12/05/1976; wsyr_radio_815; guests Sid Johnson, Jan Edison; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: The Concert Drug Scene, 06/22/1978; 06/26/1978; 08/06/1978; wsyr_radio_837; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: The Elderly, 06/20/1977; 07/10/1977; wsyr_radio_829; guest Kevin McDowel [?]; note on box reads: "TV intro and close"; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: The Elderly. 39 and Holding, 10/21/1977; 10/27/1977; 11/13/1977; 11/27/1977; wsyr_radio_832; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:20 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: The Power Problem, 02/15/1976; wsyr_radio_538; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 19)
  - Newsprobe: The Steam Plant, 06/15/1978; 06/19/1978; wsyr_radio_836; note reads: "Length: 22:30; Edited from TV 28:50"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:30 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Transportation, 12/22/1976; 12/26/1976; wsyr_radio_817; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Unemployment ... Looking for Work, 07/20/1978; 07/24/1978; 08/20/1978; wsyr_radio_838; guests Bruce Pierce, State Labor Department, Ruth Isaacs, County Social Service, Michael Tierney, Syracuse Manpower, Peter Maylone, Peace; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: United Fund, 07/14/1976; 07/29/1976; 08/08/1976; wsyr_radio_812; guests: Panadic [?], Fairbank [?]; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 43)
  - Newsprobe: Update the School Drug Scene, 04/17/1978; 05/21/1978; wsyr_radio_834; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Weather, 08/20/1976; 09/17/1976; 09/19/1976; wsyr_radio_813; guests: Dr. Herkinton [?] and Dr. Delaubenfels [?]; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Newsprobe: Welfare, 06/06/1977; 06/19/1977; wsyr_radio_828; guests: Lascaris, Heins, Brown; special program audio dub for radio; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Welfare Crisis, 12/14/1977; 12/30/1977; 01/15/1978; 02/05/1978; wsyr_radio_833; guests John Mulroy and Minch Lewis; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:50 (Box 45)
  - Newsprobe: Welfare Fraud, 09/22/1977; 10/02/1977; wsyr_radio_831; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Night Watch Programs weeks 1, 2 & 7, 1975; wsyr_radio_700; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
    Week 1: Program 1: Julie's Living Death (Care), Script 1: Kava Coffe; Program 2: George’s Private Portrait (Consumer Information); Script 63: Penzoil; Program 3: The Manner’s Dream House - Chard (Radio Free Europe); Script 9: Wrigley; Program 4: Tom & Christy - Snowed in in the Adirondaks (Department of Transportation); Script 13: Haines; Program 5: Minnie Kline’s Cut Out (American Optometric Association); Script 50: Kelly Tires; Week 2: Program 3: Subway Shadower (Junior Achievement); Script 59: Wrigley; Program 2: Champion’s Club (Religion in American Life); Script 21: Penzoil; Program 4: Alabama Summer (American Cancer Society, Virginia Graham; Week 7: Program 1: Old John Hart - Stroke (Food and Drug Administration); Script: One a day vitamin
  - Night Watch Programs: 1 thru 14, with host Peter Lee, 1975; wsyr_radio_701; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 79:20 (Box 34)